Preliminary Inventory of the Marek Lehnert Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Sound recordings of interviews and events, 1984-1996; 137 audio cassettes (Box 7-10)
  - Sound recording of Poles in Malta, 25-27 May 1990; Use copy reference number: 2002c12_a_0006389 (Box 10)
  - Sound recording from Wrocław and of Cardinal Henryk Gulbinowicz, March - April 1990 (Box 10)
    Side A: Wrocław, Poland, March 1990.
    Side B: Cardinal Gulbinowicz in Rome, 4 April 1990. Use copy reference number: 2002c12_a_0006390
  - Sound recording of Pope John Paul II leaving the hospital and Father Michał Heller, 28 July - 31 October 1992 (Box 10)
    Side A: The Pope leaves the hospital, 28 July 1992.
    Side B: Father Heller talks about the Pontifical Academy of Sciences, 31 October 1992. Use copy reference number: 2002c12_a_0006392
  - Sound recording of Father Henryk Hoser and radio broadcast including interview with a primate (bishop), 12 December 1992 - 1 January 1993 (Box 10)
    Side A: Hoser, 12 December 1992.
    Side B: Radio broadcast Kościół i Świat (Church and the World), which includes an interview with a primate (bishop), 1 January 1993. Use copy reference number: 2002c12_a_0006393
  - Sound recording of Marek Lehnert reporting from a refugee camp in Latina, Italy, 9-16 August 1987 (Box 10)
    Lehnert reports from a refugee camp "Zanim Pojadą Dalej" (Before They Go Further) in Latina, Italy. These broadcasts are from 9 and 16 August 1987. Use copy reference number: 2002c12_a_0006395
  - Sound recording of Father Konrad Hejmo, 20 September 1988; Use copy reference number: 2002c12_a_0006396 (Box 10)
  - Sound recording of Sister Akwina Filipowicz, 9 November 1989 (Box 10)
    Filipowicz talks about Brother Albert, Rome. Use copy reference number: 2002c12_a_0006397
  - Sound recording of Professor Jerzy Janik, Bishop Szczepan Wesoły, and B. Michałek, 13-15 August 1990 (Box 10)
    Side A: Professor Jerzy Janik talks about Castel Gandolfo, 13 August 1990.
    Side B: Polish Bishop Szczepan Wesoły and B. Michałek, 15 August 1990. Use copy reference number: 2002c12_a_0006398
  - Sound recording of Father Kazimierz Jancarz and Bishop Ignacy Tokarczuk, 5-6 December 1990 (Box 10)
    Side A: Father Kazimierz Jancarz talks about his group, 5 December 1990.
    Side B: Bishop Ignacy Tokarczuk, 6 December 1990. Use copy reference number: 2002c12_a_0006400
  - Sound recording of Cardinal Józef Glemp and Bishop Henryk Muszyński, 24-27 September 1990 (Box 10)
    Side A: Glemp, Rome, 24 September 1990.
    Side B: Muszyński talks about the Vatican Synod, 27 September 1990. Use copy reference number: 2002c12_a_0006401
  - Sound recording of Radio Vatican broadcast of the Pope's appeal to the Poles, 8 May - 29 August 1989 (Box 10)
    Side A: Radio Vatican broadcast of Pope John Paul II's appeal to the Poles, 8 May, 19 May, 3 August 1989.
    Side B: Radio Vatican broadcast (continuation), 26 August 1989. Use copy reference number: 2002c12_a_0006403
  - Sound recording of Cardinal Józef Glemp and Archbishop Józef Michalik Kaczyński, 1993 (Box 10)
    Side A: Glemp in Assisi.
    Side B: Kaczyński, Pałasińska. Use copy reference number: 2002c12_a_0006404
  - Sound recording of Jerzy Kluger, Archbishop John Foley, and Roman Rota (part II), 10-18 March 1993 (Box 10)
    Side A: Jerzy Kluger, Polish businessman in Rome, and Archbishop John Foley, March 10 and 18, 1993.
    Side B: Roman Rota (part II). Use copy reference number: 2002c12_a_0006406
  - Sound recording of Father Michał Heller, Danuta Wałęsa, and Father Henryk Jankowski, 4-6 October 1991 (Box 10)
    Side A: Heller in the Vatican, 4 October 1991.
    Side B: Wałęsa and Jankowski in Rome, 6 October 1991. Use copy reference number: 2002c12_a_0006408
  - Sound recording of Jan Wojciech Góra and Father Bolesław Krawczyk, 26 September - 1 October 1991 (Box 10)
    Side A: Góra, Dominican, Roman Catholic priest, Doctor of Theology, and academic chaplain, talks about the Jasna Góra Monastery.
    Side B: Krawczyk talks about the papal ceremonial, Rome, 1 October 1991. Use copy reference number: 2002c12_a_0006409